{
    "exam_metadata": {
        "layout": "exam",
        "title": "Practice Exam 18",
        "exam_id": 18,
        "courseName": "AWS Cloud Practitioner",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "tags": [
            "aws",
            "cloud"
        ],
        "description": "Introduction exam"
    },
    "questions": [
        {
            "question_number": 2,
            "question_text": "How can an AWS user with an AWS Basic Support plan obtain technical assistance from AWS?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Discussion Forums",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Senior Support Engineers"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Technical Account Managers"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Trusted Advisor"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Discussion Forums"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 3,
            "question_text": "Which of the following are pillars of the AWS Well-Architected Framework? (Choose two.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B, C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Performance efficiency | Security",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Multiple Availability Zones"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Performance efficiency"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Security"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Encryption usage"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "High availability"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 4,
            "question_text": "After selecting an Amazon EC2 Dedicated Host reservation, which pricing option would provide the largest discount?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "All upfront payment",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "No upfront payment"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Hourly on-demand payment"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Partial upfront payment"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "All upfront payment"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 5,
            "question_text": "What is an advantage of deploying an application across multiple Availability Zones?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "The application will have higher availability because it can withstand a service disruption in one Availability Zone.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "There is a lower risk of service failure if a natural disaster causes a service disruption in a given AWS Region."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "The application will have higher availability because it can withstand a service disruption in one Availability Zone."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "There will be better coverage as Availability Zones are geographically distant and can serve a wider area."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "There will be decreased application latency that will improve the user experience."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 6,
            "question_text": "A Cloud Practitioner is asked how to estimate the cost of using a new application on AWS. <br/> What is the MOST appropriate response?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Direct the user to the AWS Simple Monthly Calculator for an estimate.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Inform the user that AWS pricing allows for on-demand pricing."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Direct the user to the AWS Simple Monthly Calculator for an estimate."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Use Amazon QuickSight to analyze current spending on-premises."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Use Amazon AppStream 2.0 for real-time pricing analytics."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 7,
            "question_text": "A company wants to migrate its applications to a VPC on AWS. These applications will need to access on-premises resources. <br/> What combination of actions will enable the company to accomplish this goal? (Choose two.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B, D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Build a VPN connection between an on-premises device and a virtual private gateway in the new VPC. | Connect the company's on-premises data center to AWS using AWS Direct Connect.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Use the AWS Service Catalog to identify a list of on-premises resources that can be migrated."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Build a VPN connection between an on-premises device and a virtual private gateway in the new VPC."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Use Amazon Athena to query data from the on-premises database servers."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Connect the company's on-premises data center to AWS using AWS Direct Connect."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Leverage Amazon CloudFront to restrict access to static web content provided through the company's on-premises web servers."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 8,
            "question_text": "A web application running on AWS has been spammed with malicious requests from a recurring set of IP addresses. <br/> Which AWS service can help secure the application and block the malicious traffic?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS WAF",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS IAM"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon GuardDuty"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS WAF"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 9,
            "question_text": "Treating infrastructure as code in the AWS Cloud allows users to:",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "automate the infrastructure provisioning process.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "automate migration of on-premises hardware to AWS data centers."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "let a third party automate an audit of the AWS infrastructure."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "turn over application code to AWS so it can run on the AWS infrastructure."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "automate the infrastructure provisioning process."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 10,
            "question_text": "A company requires a dedicated network connection between its on-premises servers and the AWS Cloud. <br/> Which AWS service should be used?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Direct Connect",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS VPN"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Direct Connect"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon API Gateway"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Connect"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 11,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service can be used to query stored datasets directly from Amazon S3 using standard SQL?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon Athena",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Glue"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Data Pipeline"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon CloudSearch"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Athena"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 12,
            "question_text": "AWS CloudFormation is designed to help the user:",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "model and provision resources.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "model and provision resources."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "update application code."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "set up data lakes."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "create reports for billing."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 13,
            "question_text": "Which of the following is an AWS database service?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon Redshift",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Redshift"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon S3 Glacier"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Snowball"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 14,
            "question_text": "A Cloud Practitioner must determine if any security groups in an AWS account have been provisioned to allow unrestricted access for specific ports. <br/> What is the SIMPLEST way to do this?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Run AWS Trusted Advisor and review the findings.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Review the inbound rules for each security group in the Amazon EC2 management console to check for port 0.0.0.0/0."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Run AWS Trusted Advisor and review the findings."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Open the AWS IAM console and check the inbound rule filters for open access."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "In AWS Config, create a custom rule that invokes an AWS Lambda function to review rules for inbound access."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 15,
            "question_text": "What are the benefits of developing and running a new application in the AWS Cloud compared to on-premises? (Choose two.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C, D",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS makes it easy to architect for high availability. | AWS can easily accommodate application demand changes.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS automatically distributes the data globally for higher durability."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS will take care of operating the application."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS makes it easy to architect for high availability."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS can easily accommodate application demand changes."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "AWS takes care application security patching."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 16,
            "question_text": "A user needs an automated security assessment report that will identify unintended network access to Amazon EC2 instances and vulnerabilities on those instances. <br/> Which AWS service will provide this assessment report?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon Inspector",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "EC2 security groups"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Config"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Macie"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Inspector"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 17,
            "question_text": "How can a company isolate the costs of production and non-production workloads on AWS?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Use different accounts for production and non-production expenses.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Create Identity and Access Management (IAM) roles for production and non-production workloads."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Use different accounts for production and non-production expenses."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Use Amazon EC2 for non-production workloads and other services for production workloads."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Use Amazon CloudWatch to monitor the use of services."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 18,
            "question_text": "Where can users find a catalog of AWS-recognized providers of third-party security solutions?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Marketplace",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Service Catalog"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Marketplace"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Quick Start"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS CodeDeploy"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 19,
            "question_text": "A Cloud Practitioner needs to store data for 7 years to meet regulatory requirements. <br/> Which AWS service will meet this requirement at the LOWEST cost?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon S3 Glacier",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon S3"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Snowball"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Redshift"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon S3 Glacier"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 20,
            "question_text": "What are the immediate benefits of using the AWS Cloud? (Choose two.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C, D",
            "correct_answer_text": "User control of infrastructure. | Increased agility.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Increased IT staff."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Capital expenses are replaced with variable expenses."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "User control of infrastructure."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Increased agility."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "AWS holds responsibility for security in the cloud."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 21,
            "question_text": "Which security service automatically recognizes and classifies sensitive data or intellectual property on AWS?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon Macie",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon GuardDuty"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Macie"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Inspector"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Shield"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 22,
            "question_text": "What is the purpose of AWS Storage Gateway?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "It connects on-premises data storage to the AWS Cloud.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "It ensures on-premises data storage is 99.999999999% durable."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "It transports petabytes of data to and from AWS."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "It connects to multiple Amazon EC2 instances."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "It connects on-premises data storage to the AWS Cloud."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 23,
            "question_text": "What should users do if they want to install an application in geographically isolated locations?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Deploy the application to multiple AWS Regions.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Install the application using multiple internet gateways."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Deploy the application to an Amazon VPC."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Deploy the application to multiple AWS Regions."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Configure the application using multiple NAT gateways."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 24,
            "question_text": "A system in the AWS Cloud is designed to withstand the failure of one or more components. <br/> What is this an example of?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "High Availability",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Elasticity"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "High Availability"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Scalability"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Agility"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 25,
            "question_text": "A Cloud Practitioner needs a consistent and dedicated connection between AWS resources and an on-premises system. <br/> Which AWS service can fulfill this requirement?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Direct Connect",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Direct Connect"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS VPN"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Connect"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Data Pipeline"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 26,
            "question_text": "Within the AWS shared responsibility model, who is responsible for security and compliance?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS and the customer share responsibility.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "The customer is responsible."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS is responsible."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS and the customer share responsibility."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS shares responsibility with the relevant governing body."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 27,
            "question_text": "To use the AWS CLI, users are required to generate:",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "an access/secret key.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "a password policy."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "an access/secret key."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "a managed policy."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "an API key."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 28,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service is used to provide encryption for Amazon EBS?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS KMS",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Certificate Manager"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Systems Manager"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS KMS"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Config"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 29,
            "question_text": "How does AWS charge for AWS Lambda usage once the free tier has been exceeded? (Choose two.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A, C",
            "correct_answer_text": "By the time it takes for the Lambda function to execute. | By the number of requests made for a given Lambda function.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "By the time it takes for the Lambda function to execute."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "By the number of versions of a specific Lambda function."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "By the number of requests made for a given Lambda function."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "By the programming language that is used for the Lambda function."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "By the total number of Lambda functions in an AWS account."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 30,
            "question_text": "Which of the following describes the relationships among AWS Regions, Availability Zones, and edge locations? (Choose two.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B, E",
            "correct_answer_text": "There are more edge locations than AWS Regions. | There are more Availability Zones than AWS Regions.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "There are more AWS Regions than Availability Zones."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "There are more edge locations than AWS Regions."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "An edge location is an Availability Zone."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "There are more AWS Regions than edge locations."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "There are more Availability Zones than AWS Regions."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 31,
            "question_text": "What does AWS Shield Standard provide?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "DDoS protection",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "WAF rules"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "DDoS protection"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Identity and Access Management (IAM) permissions and access to resources"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Data encryption"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 32,
            "question_text": "A company wants to build its new application workloads in the AWS Cloud instead of using on-premises resources. <br/> What expense can be reduced using the AWS Cloud?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "hardware required to support new applications",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "The cost of writing custom-built Java or Node .js code"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Penetration testing for security"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "hardware required to support new applications"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Writing specific test cases for third-party applications."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 33,
            "question_text": "What does AWS Marketplace allow users to do? (Choose two.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B, C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Sell solutions to other AWS users. | Buy third-party software that runs on AWS.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Sell unused Amazon EC2 Spot Instances."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Sell solutions to other AWS users."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Buy third-party software that runs on AWS."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Purchase AWS security and compliance documents."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Order AWS Snowball."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 34,
            "question_text": "What does it mean if a user deploys a hybrid cloud architecture on AWS?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Some resources run on-premises and some run in the AWS Cloud.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "All resources run using on-premises infrastructure."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Some resources run on-premises and some run in a colocation center."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "All resources run in the AWS Cloud."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Some resources run on-premises and some run in the AWS Cloud."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 35,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service allows users to identify the changes made to a resource over time?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Config",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Inspector"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Config"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Service Catalog"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS IAM"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 36,
            "question_text": "How can a company reduce its Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) using AWS?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "By minimizing large capital expenditures",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "By minimizing large capital expenditures"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "By having no responsibility for third-party license costs"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "By having no operational expenditures"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "By having AWS manage applications"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 37,
            "question_text": "Which activity is a customer responsibility in the AWS Cloud according to the AWS shared responsibility model?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Ensuring Amazon EBS volumes are backed up",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Ensuring network connectivity from AWS to the internet"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Patching and fixing flaws within the AWS Cloud infrastructure"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Ensuring the physical security of cloud data centers"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Ensuring Amazon EBS volumes are backed up"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 38,
            "question_text": "What are the advantages of the AWS Cloud? (Choose two.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B, C",
            "correct_answer_text": "No need to guess capacity requirements | Increased speed to market",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Fixed rate monthly cost"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "No need to guess capacity requirements"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Increased speed to market"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Increased upfront capital expenditure"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Physical access to cloud data centers"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 39,
            "question_text": "When comparing the total cost of ownership (TCO) of an on-premises infrastructure to a cloud architecture, what costs should be considered? (Choose two.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B, C",
            "correct_answer_text": "The cost of purchasing and installing server hardware in the on-premises data. | The cost of administering the infrastructure, including operating system and software installations, patches, backups, and recovering from failures.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "The credit card processing fees for application transactions in the cloud."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "The cost of purchasing and installing server hardware in the on-premises data."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "The cost of administering the infrastructure, including operating system and software installations, patches, backups, and recovering from failures."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "The costs of third-party penetration testing."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "The advertising costs associated with an ongoing enterprise-wide campaign."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 40,
            "question_text": "Which AWS feature allows a company to take advantage of usage tiers for services across multiple member accounts?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Consolidated billing",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Service control policies (SCPs)"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Consolidated billing"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "All Upfront Reserved Instances"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Cost Explorer"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 41,
            "question_text": "What is one of the customer's responsibilities according to the AWS shared responsibility model?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Application security",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Virtualization infrastructure"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Network infrastructure"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Application security"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Physical security of hardware"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 42,
            "question_text": "What helps a company provide a lower latency experience to its users globally?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Using edge locations to put content closer to all users",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Using an AWS Region that is central to all users"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Using a second Availability Zone in the AWS Region that is using used"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Enabling caching in the AWS Region that is being used"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Using edge locations to put content closer to all users"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 43,
            "question_text": "How can the AWS Cloud increase user workforce productivity after migration from an on-premises data center?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "Users do not have to wait for infrastructure provisioning.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Users do not have to wait for infrastructure provisioning."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "The AWS Cloud infrastructure is much faster than an on-premises data center infrastructure."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS takes over application configuration management on behalf of users."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Users do not need to address security and compliance issues."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 44,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service provides a quick and automated way to create and manage AWS accounts?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Organizations",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS QuickSight"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Lightsail"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Organizations"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Connect"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 45,
            "question_text": "Which Amazon RDS feature can be used to achieve high availability?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "Multiple Availability Zones",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Multiple Availability Zones"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Reserved Instances"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Provisioned IOPS storage"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Enhanced monitoring"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 46,
            "question_text": "Where should users report that AWS resources are being used for malicious purposes?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Abuse team",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Abuse team"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Shield"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Support"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Developer Forums"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 47,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service needs to be enabled to track all user account changes within the AWS Management Console?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS CloudTrail",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS CloudTrail"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "VPC Flow Logs"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS CloudHSM"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 48,
            "question_text": "What is an AWS Cloud design best practice?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "High availability",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Tight coupling of components"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Single point of failure"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "High availability"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Overprovisioning of resources"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 49,
            "question_text": "Why is AWS more economical than traditional data centers for applications with varying compute workloads?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon EC2 instances can be launched on-demand when needed.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) costs are billed on a monthly basis."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Customers retain full administrative access to their Amazon EC2 instances."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EC2 instances can be launched on-demand when needed."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Customers can permanently run enough instances to handle peak workloads."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 50,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service would simplify migration of a database to AWS?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS)",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Storage Gateway"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS)"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2)"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon AppStream 2.0"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}